Wolf, Benjamin H. Additional Arbitration Files 5539
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 77-96 State of New York Department of Correctional Services vs. Willie Washington, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  11/8/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Absences, excessive; Tardiness; Improper Maintenance of Records.
- 77-97 State of New York Office of Employee Relations (OER) vs. Duncan, Wardel et. al, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  11/77. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 77-98 State of New York Office of Employee Relations (OER) vs. Michael Valencia, State University of New York (SUNY), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  8/77. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 77-99 Beachview Nursing Home vs. Medical and Health Employees Union, Local #4, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  10/11/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination--Unsatisfactory Work.
- 77-100 Chrysler Manhattan vs. District 15, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  10/27/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Theft.
- 77-101 State of New York Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- 77-102 State of New York Office of Employee Relations (OER) vs. Snyder and Procopio, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  11/77. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 77-103 New York City Board of Education vs. Council of Supervisors and Administrators, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  11/29/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Arbitrability--Grievance.
- 77-104 State of New York Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  9/77. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 77-105 City of New York vs. District Council 37, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- 77-106 E.R. Squibb and Sons Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers' Union (ICWU), Local 626, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- 77-107 State of New York Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- 77-108 American Guild of Variety Artists, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  9/77. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Election certification.
- 77-109 State of New York Department of Corrections vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  11/25/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discharge--Drugs, Sale.
- 77-110 Parsons Footwear Corporation vs. AFL-CIO Retail Clerks International Union, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- 77-111 Ted Bates and Company, vs. Screen Actors Guild, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  12/28/77. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Evidence-- Burden of Proof.
- 77-112 Suffolk County Department of Labor vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Town of Brookhaven, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  12/9/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Classification of Job, temporary.
- 77-113 State of New York Department of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1977 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  11/15/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination of Job--Fights and Altercations.
- 77-114 Capital Mail Chute Corporation vs. Shopmen's Local Union #555, International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (IABOIW), Local 455, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  1/78. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 77-115 New York City Board of Education vs. Ms. Virginia Sims, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  12/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Tardiness; Incompetence--Inefficiency; Improper Job Conduct.
- 77-116 Danbury Board of Education vs. Danbury Education Association, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  12/1/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Classification of Jobs, Added Duties.
- 77-117 Pan American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  12/28/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Recall--Physical Disability.
- 77-118 TWA vs. Air Line Pilots Association, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  12/23/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension-- Call-In--Availability.
- 77-119 Fisher and Brothers Incorporated vs. Local 814, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  11/16/77. Arbitrator's Notes, Routine Correspondence, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct--Indecent Conduct.
- 77-120 Kaufman Iron Works Incorporated vs. Shopmen's Local Union #455, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  12/77. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Cancelled.
- 77-121 State of New York vs. Security and Law Enforcement Council 82, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  11/29/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct--Drinking.
- 77-122 State of New Jersey vs. Hunterdon State School, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council #1, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  11/12/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Improper Personal Conduct--Assault.
- 77-123 Interstate United Hospital Dietetics, Incorporated vs. Service Employees International Union, Local #144, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  5/80. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 77-124 Ted Bates and Company vs. Screen Actors' Guild, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- 77-125 Jersey City State College vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  7/6/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Failure to Qualify.
- 77-126 Jersey City State College vs. McCoy, Stimson, Bailey et. al, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  10/77. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 77-127 Owens-Illinois vs. International Printing and Graphic Communications Union, Local 447, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  12/15/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Transfer-Probation.
- 77-128 Texaco Incorporated vs. Petroleum Trades Employees Union, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  2/22/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, AM. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules; Insubordination; Fights and Altercations.
- 77-129 Bellmore-Merrick Central High School District (CHSD) vs. Bellmore-Merrick United Secondary Teachers (UST), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  12/77. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 77-130 Exxon Company USA vs. Industrial Employees Association, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  12/9/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discharge--Drinking
- 77-131 Pratt Institute vs. United Federation of College Teachers, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), Local 1460, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- 77-132 New Jersey vs. New Jersey State Troopers Association, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  7/31/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Promotion--Failure to Qualify
- 77-133 Jersey City State College vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  7/12/78. Routine Correspondence, ES, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Failure to Qualify.
- 77-134 Exxon Company, U.S.A. vs. Local 877, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  4/78. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 77-135 State of New York vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) (Letchworth-Walter Brown), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  4/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 77-136 Western Publishing Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), Local 1598, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  8/4/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Overtime--Failure to Schedule.
- 78-1 J. & M. Knitting Corporation vs. International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  1/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-2 Gayrand Knitting Mills vs. International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- 78-3 Head Knitting Mills, Incorporated vs. International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- 78-4 Humik Fabrics Corporation vs. International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- 78-5 Coronet Manufacturing Corporation vs. International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- 78-6 New Brunswick Tool and Die vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), District 15, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  4/28/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Promotion--Qualifications.
- 78-7 Central Islip Teachers' Association vs. Central Islip Board of Education, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  8/77. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Settled.
- 78-8 Mosler Airmatic and Electronic Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 102, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  5/12/78. Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules--Safety; Insubordination.
- 78-9 State of New York vs. Fred Baganz, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  2/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-10 Brookhaven-Comeswaque Union Free School District (UFSD) #3 vs. Pt. Jefferson Teachers' Association, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  6/9/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Leaves of Absence--Maternity Leave--Extension.
- 78-11 South Westbury Union Free School District (UFSD) vs. Westbury Teachers Association, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  5/78. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 78-12 Schenectady City School District vs. Schenectady Federation of Teachers, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  5/12/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Qualifications.
- 78-13 Bethpage Union Free School District (UFSD) vs. Bethpage Congress of Teachers, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  6/3/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties.
- 78-14 New York State Department of Mental Hygiene, vs. Council 82, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1a)
  4/18/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Agreements. Issue: Suspension--Assault.
- 78-15 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  5/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Settled.
- 78-16 Schenectady Union Free School District vs. Schenectady Federation of Teachers, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  5/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-17 U.S. Division of Military and Naval Affairs vs. New York Council of the Association of Civilian Technicians, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  9/18/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, TR. Issue: Promotion--Vacancy--Posting.
- 78-18 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  7/9/79. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreement, Supporting Documents, TR. Issue: Evaluation of Job Factors--Improper Evaluation.
- 78-19 Tenneco Chemicals, Incorporated vs. Employees Association of Heyden Newport Chemical Corporation, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  5/26/78, Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Discharge--Fights and Altercations--Threats.
- 78-20 Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  5/79. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 78-21 John Stuart Incorporated vs. United Storeworkers Local 3, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  6/19/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Management Rights--Customer Relations; Supervisors and Foremen--Bargaining Unit Work.
- 78-22 TRW, Martin Rockwell Division vs. Local 338, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- 78-23 Allen Manufacturing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 518, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  6/8/78. Exhibits, Routine Correspondence, AM. Issue: Suspension--Absences, excessive.
- 78-24 Dan's Supreme Super Market vs. Local 1500, Retail Clerks International Union, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  5/24/82. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Maintenance of Records.
- 78-25 Ashland Chemical Company vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Local 8-917, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  7/14/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Sleeping on the Job
- 78-26 State of New York vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) (re: Regis Mull), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  4/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-27 State of New York Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  4/79. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 78-28 First National City Bank vs. Local 94-94a, International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  4/79. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-29 E.I. Dupont de Nemours and Company vs. Parlin Employees Association, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  7/14/78. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Unsatisfactory Work.
- 78-30 Board of Education of City of New York vs. Celia Uhrman, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  10/27/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Suspension--Incompetence and Inefficiency.
- 78-31 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers NCO (Non-Commissioned Officers'?) Association, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  8/11/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Transcripts, Supporting Documents. Issue: Transfer--Discipline--Improper Personal Conduct
- 78-32 Council of Supervisors and Administrators vs. Board of Education of City of New York, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  11/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Withdrawn
- 78-33 Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. Federation of Westinghouse Salaried Unions, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  4/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 78-34 AVCO Lycoming Division vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 376, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  11/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-35 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation, Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  8/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-36 State of New York Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  7/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-37 State of New York Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  7/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-38 State of New York, Office of Employee Relations (OER) vs. Peter Mendleson, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  5/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-39 Lakeland Board of Education vs. Lakeland Federation of Teachers, Local 1760, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  10/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-40 State of New York Department of Correctional Services vs. Security and Law Enforcement Council 82, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1978 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  6/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-41 Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. National Westinghouse Conference, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- 78-42 State of New York, State University at Buffalo vs. United University Professions, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  2/16/79. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Arbitrability.
- 78-43 Patrolmen's Benevolent Association of New York City vs. City of New York Office of Municipal Labor Relations, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  9/5/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Overtime--Rates of Pay.
- 78-44 Cushman and Wakefield vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 56, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  7/3/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Layoff--Recall--Seniority.
- 78-45 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association (STFA), Arbitration, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  5/78. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-46 State of New Jersey vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association, Police, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  7/10/78. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Transfers--Assignment of Jobs.
- 78-47 New York State Department of Correctional Services vs. Security and Law Enforcement Council 82, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  11/20/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Absences, excessive.
- 78-48 Hebrew National Kosher Foods vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Local 627, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  9/26/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Management Rights--Working Rules--Contracts.
- 78-49 City of Mt. Vernon vs. Uniformed Fire Fighters Association, Incorporated, Local 107, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  11/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-50 Flock Industries Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  9/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-51 New York City Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. Local 1549, District Council 37, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  9/80. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Settled.
- 78-52 Collyer Insulated Wire vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 1098, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  7/3/77. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreement, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Management Rights.
- 78-53 Arlington Central School District vs. Arlington's Teachers' Association, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  9/31/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Health and Welfare Programs.
- 78-54 Newark Morning Ledger Company vs. Newark Typographical Union, Local 103, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- 78-55 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  6/78. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-56 State of New York vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  9/7/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Demotion--Discipline.
- 78-57 State of New York Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- 78-58 State of New York Office of Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  7/78. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 78-59 Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) vs. State of New York Department of Mental Hygiene, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  7/25/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discipline--Disloyalty--Improper Maintenance of Records.
- 78-60 Artcarved Incorporated vs. International Jewelry Workers Union, Local #1, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  8/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Discipline--Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 78-61 Town of Marlborough and Police vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees AFSCME), Council 82, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  7/78. Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 78-62 State of New York Department of Correctional Services vs. Security and Law Enforcement, Council 82, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- 78-63 Jacobsun Manufacturing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 1992, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  8/9/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Seniority--Termination of Seniority.
- 78-64 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  8/11/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 78-65 State of New York Department of Correctional Services vs. Charles Corey, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- 78-66 State of New York Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  7/19/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-67 Questor Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 177, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  9/11/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Threats.
- 78-68 (empty folder) Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association (PBA) (Box 26, Folder 24)
- 78-69 Mamaronek Board of Education vs. Mamaroneck Teachers' Association, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  12/1/78. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-70 City of New York Office of Municipal Labor Relations vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  7/28/78. Agreements. Settled.
- 78-71 Manhasset Union Free School vs. Manhasset Teachers' Association, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  9/26/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Work Outside Unit.
- 78-72 State of New York Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  8/29/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 78-73 Texaco Incorporated vs. Petroleum Trades Employees Union, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  2/27/78. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 78-74 Pius XII School vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 338, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  10/6/78. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Rates of Pay--Inequities--Classification of Job.
- 78-75 WPIX vs. American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  11/30/78. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, ES. Issue: Suspension-- Unsatisfactory Work--Improper Maintenance of Records.
- 78-76 Slant Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), Local 485, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  12/78. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 78-77 Schwartz Brothers Memorial Chapel, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 1034, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  10/16/78. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct.
- 78-78 New York City Office of Labor Relations vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, Local 1549, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  12/6/78. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents, Exhibits. Issue: Vacation--Unauthorized--Vacation Pay.
- 78-79 New York State Office of Mental Health vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 35)